Privacy Policy
==============

Apeaksoft Studio is committed to providing you with the highest level of protection for your data and privacy. We only collect data when it's truly necessary, and in our customers' best interests, e.g.: to send you a product activation code via email. By no means will the collected data be sold or for any other reason given to third parties. The following statement give you an overview of how we ensure this protection and what kind of data is being collected for what purpose.

### Website

You can visit most areas of the Apeaksoft website without disclosing any personal information.

Apeaksoft only logs the domain name, IP address and browser type of our website visitors via our web server log files and analytics tools at irregular intervals. We use this information to log global access to our website.

For certain features we will ask that you provide Apeaksoft certain information so that it works properly. You can decide at any time whether you would like to continue with an instruction prompting you to provide information. In some cases, you will be unable to complete a particular step in the process if you do not want to provide the information requested. For example, we will ask for personal information in the following instances:

• If you place an order through our online store, we will ask you to provide information required for processing the order. This may include your name, address, email address, and credit card number or bank details.  
• If you subscribe to a newsletter. If you signed up for a newsletter and no longer want to receive it, you can unsubscribe at any time by using the unsubscribe option provided in the email or by sending us an email using the contact information provided below.

### Cookies

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer or in your browser. Cookies are loaded on your browser when you first use a product or service. Cookies do not include any personal information. We may use cookies to identify the browser you are using so that our website displays properly. We also use cookies in various places on our website in order to document your visit to the Apeaksoft website and allow for a more efficient website design.

If you do not want to allow Apeaksoft or someone else to use cookies, you can disable cookie installation via your browser setting. While you also have the option of deleting cookies from your computer's hard disk at any time, if you choose to do so, you may be unable to use some of the features of our website, products and services.

### eCommerce

Apeaksoft uses secure server hosted by MYCOMMERCE, Paddle and other 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt the entire customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

You can help us by also taking precautions to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure web browser like Safari.

• To secure your information in transmission we use Secure Sockets Layer software (SSL) where needed. This software encrypts the information you submit.  
• Of course this is also true for credit card payments. The credit card information is only stored temporarily and deleted after being handed on to the respective payment provider  
• It is important for you to take precautions against unauthorized access to your password and your computer. If you share your computer with others, you should remember to always log off after each session.

### MYCOMMERCE

MYCOMMERCE is an online payment processor that is the best Paypal alternative for global businesses. It offers numerous payment options and currencies, including phone and fax order support in 16 countries. Apeaksoft uses MYCOMMERCE to make it easier for you to buy products.

### Paddle

Paddle is the another Merchant of Record for all our orders. Paddle provides all customer service inquiries and handles returns. Payments information (these include name, location, contact details, and billing information) provided by you will be stored and processed by Paddle.com. All such information is subject to the privacy policy of Paddle.com (available here https://paddle.com/privacy ).

### Software Installation and Activation

Activation, trial extension and unlocking of free software is achieved through an activation routine at program launch. This process requires purchased email address and a license key.

Activation of a full version software requires an active Internet connection. During the process, a connection to a licensing server is established and a validity check performed. Invalid licenses / license keys or keys that have been used multiple times will result in the display of a licensing error in the program that will disappear once the program has been activated successfully. The validity of a product license will be automatically checked online at regular intervals.

The following information is transmitted when you activate a program with a license key:

• The license key  
• A checksum  
• The product code  
• The version numbers

### Third-party Analytics Tools

Google Analytics

We use the following third-party analytics tools to better understand your interaction with our website and use of our products/services. Our ultimate goal is to create a more user-friendly experience for you:

We use Google Analytics, a web analysis service from Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses Cookies to make it possible to analyze your use of our website. Information about your use of our website the Cookie generates is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and saved there. However, before this happens, Google shortens and anonymizes your IP address (Google's anonymize IP process) if located within a member state of the European Union or in other contracting member states to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. The entire IP address is transferred to a Google server in the USA and saved there only in exceptional cases.

This anonymization ensures that your IP address cannot be traced back to you. Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website in order to compile reports about website activities for Apeaksoft and provide additional services associated with website and Internet usage. Google can transfer this information to third parties, where appropriate, if legally mandated or if Google contracts with third parties to process such data. Google will not associate your IP address with other Google data. By using our website, you expressly consent to Google's collection and storage of your data in the manner and for the purposes described above.

You also have the option to prevent Google from acquiring and processing data generated by Cookies and data related to your use of our website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing a Google-provided browser plugin.

More information about Google Analytics can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en).

### Other

• Protection of Apeaksoft and third parties: We will disclose accounts and personal data of customers, if we are bound by law to do so or if disclosure is necessary to enforce our General Terms and Conditions or other agreements or to protect our rights or the rights of third parties. This includes data exchange with companies specializing in preventing and minimizing the risk of violation and credit card fraud. We explicitly state that in this context no data will be passed on to those companies for economic use that would contradict this privacy policy.  
• With your consent: In all other cases we will inform you if personal information is to be handed off to third parties and give you the chance to give your consent.
